(function(){"use strict";var e={3751:function(e,t,n){var s=n(7195),o=function(){var e=this,t=e._self._c,n=e._self._setupProxy;return t("main",{staticClass:"app"},[t("h1",[e._v("My VUE.js quiz")]),n.quizIsDone?t("section",[t("h2",{staticClass:"congrats"},[e._v("You have finished my VUE.js quiz!")]),t("p",{staticClass:"score"},[e._v("Your score is "+e._s(n.score)+" / "+e._s(n.questions.length))])]):t("section",{staticClass:"quiz"},[t("div",{staticClass:"quiz-info"},[t("span",{staticClass:"question"},[e._v(" "+e._s(n.getCurrentQuestion.question)+" ")]),t("span",{staticClass:"score"},[e._v(" Score "+e._s(n.score)+" / "+e._s(n.questions.length)+" ")])]),t("div",{staticClass:"options"},e._l(n.getCurrentQuestion.options,(function(s,o){return t("label",{key:o,class:`option ${n.getCurrentQuestion.selected==o?o==n.getCurrentQuestion.answer?"correct":"incorrect":""} ${null!=n.getCurrentQuestion.selected&&o!=n.getCurrentQuestion.selected?"disabled":""}`},[t("input",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:n.getCurrentQuestion.selected,expression:"getCurrentQuestion.selected"}],attrs:{type:"radio",name:n.getCurrentQuestion.index,disabled:n.getCurrentQuestion.selected},domProps:{value:o,checked:e._q(n.getCurrentQuestion.selected,o)},on:{change:[function(t){return e.$set(n.getCurrentQuestion,"selected",o)},n.answerSet]}}),t("span",[e._v(" "+e._s(s)+" ")])])})),0),t("div",{staticClass:"lower-info"},[t("button",{attrs:{disabled:!n.getCurrentQuestion.selected},on:{click:n.nextQuestion}},[e._v(" "+e._s(n.getCurrentQuestion.index==n.questions.length-1?"Check for results":null==n.getCurrentQuestion.selected?"Select an option":"Next question")+" ")]),t("span",{staticClass:"progress"},[e._v(" Question "+e._s(n.currentQuestion+1)+" / "+e._s(n.questions.length)+" ")])])])])},i=[],r={__name:"App",setup(e){const t=(0,s.iH)([{question:"What is the primary purpose of Vue.js in web development?",answer:2,options:["To serve as a back-end server","To handle database operations","To manage state and build user interfaces"],selected:null},{question:"Which directive in Vue.js is used for two-way data binding?",answer:1,options:["v-show","v-model","v-bind"],selected:null},{question:'What does the "v-for" directive in Vue.js do?',answer:0,options:["Loops through an array to render elements","Adds an event listener","Defines a computed property"],selected:null},{question:'Vue.js, what is the purpose of the "computed" property?',answer:0,options:["It computes derived state based on reactive dependencies","It sets up routes for navigation","It defines methods to handle user input"],selected:null},{question:'What does the "v-if" directive in Vue.js do?',answer:1,options:["Adds an event listener","Conditionally renders an element","Defines a computed property"],selected:null},{question:'In Vue.js, what is the purpose of the "v-bind" directive?',answer:1,options:["Adds an event listener","Binds an attribute or property to an expression","Sets up routes for navigation"],selected:null},{question:'What is the role of the "watch" option in a Vue component?',answer:1,options:["Handles form submissions","Observes changes to data properties and performs actions","Defines methods to handle user input"],selected:null},{question:"How can you communicate between parent and child components in Vue.js?",answer:1,options:["Using the v-if directive","Through the use of props and custom events","Defining a computed property"],selected:null},{question:"What is the purpose of the Vue Router library in Vue.js?",answer:2,options:["Manages global state in the application","Handles HTTP requests","Enables client-side routing in a single-page application"],selected:null},{question:"How do you handle user input in Vue.js forms?",answer:1,options:["Using the v-show directive","Through the use of methods and data binding","Defining a computed property"],selected:null},{question:'What is the significance of the "created" lifecycle hook in Vue.js?',answer:1,options:["Triggered after the component is added to the DOM","Executes when the component is created but before any DOM is rendered","Invoked when the component is updated"],selected:null},{question:"How do you conditionally apply styles in Vue.js?",answer:1,options:["Using the v-bind directive","Through the use of computed properties","Adding inline styles directly in the template"],selected:null},{question:'What is the purpose of the "provide" and "inject" options in Vue.js?',answer:2,options:["Sets up routes for navigation","Enables communication between sibling components","Facilitates dependency injection in deeply nested components"],selected:null},{question:"Which Vue.js feature allows you to dynamically switch between components?",answer:2,options:["The v-show directive","The v-for directive","The <component> element with dynamic components"],selected:null},{question:"Which lifecycle hook in Vue.js is triggered after the component has been added to the DOM?",answer:2,options:["beforeCreate","updated","mounted"],selected:null}]),n=(0,s.iH)(!1),o=(0,s.iH)(0),i=(0,s.Fl)((()=>{let e=0;return t.value.forEach((t=>{t.selected==t.answer&&e++})),e})),r=(0,s.Fl)((()=>{let e=t.value[o.value];return e.index=o.value,e})),u=e=>{t.value[o.value].selected=e.target.value,e.target.value=null},a=()=>{o.value<t.value.length-1?o.value++:n.value=!0};return{__sfc:!0,questions:t,quizIsDone:n,currentQuestion:o,score:i,getCurrentQuestion:r,answerSet:u,nextQuestion:a}}},u=r,a=n(1001),l=(0,a.Z)(u,o,i,!1,null,null,null),c=l.exports;s.ZP.config.productionTip=!1,new s.ZP({render:e=>e(c)}).$mount("#app")}},t={};function n(s){var o=t[s];if(void 0!==o)return o.exports;var i=t[s]={exports:{}};return e[s].call(i.exports,i,i.exports,n),i.exports}n.m=e,function(){var e=[];n.O=function(t,s,o,i){if(!s){var r=1/0;for(c=0;c<e.length;c++){s=e[c][0],o=e[c][1],i=e[c][2];for(var u=!0,a=0;a<s.length;a++)(!1&i||r>=i)&&Object.keys(n.O).every((function(e){return n.O[e](s[a])}))?s.splice(a--,1):(u=!1,i<r&&(r=i));if(u){e.splice(c--,1);var l=o();void 0!==l&&(t=l)}}return t}i=i||0;for(var c=e.length;c>0&&e[c-1][2]>i;c--)e[c]=e[c-1];e[c]=[s,o,i]}}(),function(){n.n=function(e){var t=e&&e.__esModule?function(){return e["default"]}:function(){return e};return n.d(t,{a:t}),t}}(),function(){n.d=function(e,t){for(var s in t)n.o(t,s)&&!n.o(e,s)&&Object.defineProperty(e,s,{enumerable:!0,get:t[s]})}}(),function(){n.g=function(){if("object"===typeof globalThis)return globalThis;try{return this||new Function("return this")()}catch(e){if("object"===typeof window)return window}}()}(),function(){n.o=function(e,t){return Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)}}(),function(){var e={143:0};n.O.j=function(t){return 0===e[t]};var t=function(t,s){var o,i,r=s[0],u=s[1],a=s[2],l=0;if(r.some((function(t){return 0!==e[t]}))){for(o in u)n.o(u,o)&&(n.m[o]=u[o]);if(a)var c=a(n)}for(t&&t(s);l<r.length;l++)i=r[l],n.o(e,i)&&e[i]&&e[i][0](),e[i]=0;return n.O(c)},s=self["webpackChunkquiz_app_vue"]=self["webpackChunkquiz_app_vue"]||[];s.forEach(t.bind(null,0)),s.push=t.bind(null,s.push.bind(s))}();var s=n.O(void 0,[998],(function(){return n(3751)}));s=n.O(s)})();
//# sourceMappingURL=app.c4e7ef83.js.map